<resources>
    <!-- main -->
    <string name="app_name">Self-MIEnd</string>
    <string name="app_icon">Self-MIEnd Icon</string>
    <string name="app_tagline">Guiding Your Path to\nMental Wellness</string>
    <string name="app_name2">Self-Mind, Self-Mend</string>
    <string name="app_startBtn">START</string>

    <!-- about fragment -->
    <string name="abt_hey">Hey There!</string>
    <string name="abt_intro">Self MIEnd is your personal companion on the journey to mental health and well-being. The application allows you to engage in a self-discovery process, providing a safe and supportive environment for self-reflection and personal growth. We provide self-assessment tests for common mental health problems for you to evaluate your mental well-being and determine whether professional help may be necessary.\n\n We also got you some activities and tips to try!</string>
    <string name="app_contBtn">Continue</string>
    <string name="app_backBtn">Back</string>

    <string name="home_title">Select Activity</string>
    <string name="home_testBtn">Tests</string>
    <string name="home_actBtn">Activities to Try</string>

    <!-- greeting and select test fragment -->
    <string name="tests_title">Select a Test</string>
    <string name="stressTest_title">Stress</string>
    <string name="internet_addictionTest_title">Internet\nAddiction</string>
    <string name="depressionTest_title">Depression</string>
    <string name="anxietyTest_title">Anxiety</string>

    <!--test fragment-->
    <string name="test_text">Test</string>
    <string name="test_question">Loading Question&#8230;</string>
    <string name="greeting_title">How\'s it going?</string>

    <!--result fragment-->
    <string name="test_result_title">Test Result</string>
    <string name="test_result_scoreText">Score:</string>
    <string name="test_result_severity_levelText">Severity Level:</string>
    <string name="temp_score">0</string>
    <string name="temp_level">Minimal</string>
    <string name="hotline_caption">Experiencing emotional hurdles?</string>
    <string name="hotline_call">Click for Call Support</string>
    <string name="backText">Back</string>
    <string name="nextText">Next</string>
    <string name="loading_questionText">Loading Question&#8230;</string>
    <string name="done_button">Done</string>

    <!--home fragment-->
    <string name="act_try">Activities\nto Try</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit Button</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="exit_question">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="title_activities_tips_for_mental_well_being"><![CDATA[Tips for Mental Well-being]]></string>
    <string name="self_care_for_mental_wellness">Over-all Self-care</string>
    <string name="thankyou_message">Your wellness journey matters. Thank you!</string>
    <string name="done_question">Would you like to try the other Tests and Activities?</string>
    <string name="exitButton">Exit</string>
    <string name="several_days">Several Days</string>
    <string name="not_at_all">Not at all</string>
    <string name="more_than_half_the_days">More Than Half The Days</string>
    <string name="moderately">Moderately</string>
    <string name="a_little_bit">A Little Bit</string>
    <string name="quite_a_bit">Quite A Bit</string>
    <string name="extremely">Extremely</string>
    <string name="not_applicable">Not Applicable</string>
    <string name="rarely">Rarely</string>
    <string name="occasionally">Occasionally</string>
    <string name="often">Often</string>
    <string name="always">Always</string>
    <string name="nearly_every_day">Nearly Every Day</string>
    <string name="self_care_tips_activities"><![CDATA[Self-Care Tips & Activities]]></string>
    <string name="for_specific_areas">For specific areas:</string>
    <string name="greetings">Time for a quick mental health check! Take a moment to reflect on your well-being. If you\'ve taken any assessments, we\'re here to discuss the results and provide support and guidance.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="anxiety_test_text">Anxiety Test</string>
    <string name="depression_test_text">Depression Test</string>
    <string name="stress_test_text">Stress Test</string>
    <string name="internet_addiction_test_text">Internet Addiction Test</string>
    <string name="frequently">Frequently</string>

    <string name="display_score_label">%d</string>


    <!-- Title Strings -->
    <string name="tip_title_1">1. Practice Mindfulness Meditation:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_2">2. Establish a Routine:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_3">3. Stay Connected:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_4">4. Exercise Regularly:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_5">5. Set Realistic Goals:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_6">6. Limit Screen Time:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_7">7. Prioritize Sleep:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_8">8. Express Yourself Creatively:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_9">9. Learn to Say No:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_10">10. Practice Gratitude:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_11">11. Seek Professional Support:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_12">12. Engage in Hobbies:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_13">13. Take Breaks:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_14">14. Practice Self-Compassion:\n</string>

    <!-- Description Strings -->
    <string name="tip_desc_1"><![CDATA[
    • Set aside a few minutes each day to practice mindfulness meditation.\n
    • Focus on your breath and bring your attention to the present moment.\n
    • Apps like Headspace or Calm can guide you through meditation sessions.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_2"><![CDATA[
    • Create a daily schedule that includes regular sleep, meals, and breaks.\n
    • Consistent routines can provide a sense of stability and predictability.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_3"><![CDATA[
    • Maintain relationships with friends and family.\n
    • Schedule regular social activities, even if they&apos;re virtual, to stay connected.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_4"><![CDATA[
    • Engage in physical activities you enjoy, such as walking, jogging, or yoga.\n
    • Exercise releases endorphins, which can improve your mood.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_5"><![CDATA[
    • Break down large tasks into smaller, manageable goals.\n
    • Celebrate your achievements, no matter how small.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_6"><![CDATA[
    • Set boundaries for your screen time, especially on social media.\n
    • Allocate time for activities that don&apos;t involve screens, like reading or outdoor pursuits.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_7"><![CDATA[
    • Ensure you get enough restful sleep each night.\n
    • Create a calming bedtime routine to signal to your body that it&apos;s time to wind down.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_8"><![CDATA[
    • Engage in creative activities such as writing, drawing, or playing an instrument.\n
    • Expressing yourself creatively can be therapeutic.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_9"><![CDATA[
    • Set boundaries and learn to say no when you need to.\n
    • Prioritize your well-being by not overcommitting.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_10"><![CDATA[
    • Keep a gratitude journal to reflect on positive aspects of your life.\n
    • Focus on the things you&apos;re thankful for, no matter how small.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_11"><![CDATA[
    • If needed, don&apos;t hesitate to reach out to a mental health professional.\n
    • Therapy or counseling can provide valuable tools for managing stress and challenges.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_12"><![CDATA[
    • Spend time doing things you love, whether it&apos;s gardening, painting, or playing a sport.\n
    • Hobbies can bring joy and fulfillment to your life.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_13"><![CDATA[
    • Incorporate short breaks into your day to rest and recharge.\n
    • Step away from work or stressful situations to clear your mind.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_14"><![CDATA[
    • Be kind to yourself and recognize that everyone makes mistakes.\n
    • Treat yourself with the same kindness and understanding you would offer a friend.\n
]]></string>
    <string name="selfcare_desc">Taking care of your mental well-being is crucial for overall health and happiness. Here are some selfcare activities and tips that can contribute to your mental well-being:</string>

    <string name="disclaimer"><![CDATA[The information and tools provided by this mobile application are for informational purposes only and should not be construed as medical advice or a substitute for professional mental health care. The results of any self-assessment tools should not be used to diagnose or treat any mental health condition.\n
\n
Please note that:\n
\n
The self-assessment tools in this app are not 100% accurate and may not detect all mental health conditions.
The information provided in this app is not intended to be a complete overview of mental health and may not address all of your questions or concerns.
If you are experiencing a mental health crisis, please call a suicide hotline or go to the nearest emergency room.\n
\nWe encourage you to:
\n
Use this app as a starting point for learning more about mental health.
Talk to your doctor or a mental health professional if you have any concerns about your mental health.
Take care of yourself and seek help if you need it.
\n\n
Thank you for using our app. We hope that it helps you on your journey to better mental health.
]]></string>

    <!-- Result Scoring -->

    <!-- Anxiety -->
    <string name="anxietyR1">Minimal Anxiety</string>
    <string name="anxietyR2">Mild Anxiety</string>
    <string name="anxietyR3">Moderate Anxiety</string>
    <string name="anxietyR4">Severe Anxiety</string>

    <!-- Depression -->
    <string name="depressionR1">Minimal Depression</string>
    <string name="depressionR2">Mild Depression</string>
    <string name="depressionR3">Moderate Depression</string>
    <string name="depressionR4">Moderately Severe Depression</string>
    <string name="depressionR5">Severe Depression</string>

    <!-- Internet Addiction -->
    <string name="internetAddictionR1">Normal Level of Internet Usage</string>
    <string name="internetAddictionR2">Mild Level of Internet Usage</string>
    <string name="internetAddictionR3">Moderate Level of Internet Usage</string>
    <string name="internetAddictionR4">Severe Dependence upon the Internet</string>

    <!-- Stress -->
    <string name="stressR1">Low Stress</string>
    <string name="stressR2">Moderate Stress</string>
    <string name="stressR3">High Perceived Stress</string>

    <!-- Disclaimer -->
    <string name="disclaimerHead">Disclaimer</string>

    <!-- Anxiety Tips Strings -->
    <string name="tat1">Guided Meditation and Breathing Exercises:\n</string>
    <string name="tat2">Mindfulness and Relaxation Techniques: \n</string>
    <string name="tat3">Stress-Relief Exercises:\n</string>
    <string name="tat4">Journaling or Mood Tracking:\n</string>
    <string name="tat5">Nature Sounds or Relaxing Music:\n</string>
    <string name="tat6">Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (CBT) Tools:\n</string>
    <string name="tat7">Progress Tracking and Goal Setting:\n</string>
    <string name="tat8">Virtual Support Groups or Forums:\n</string>
    <string name="tat9">Stress Assessments or Coping Strategies:\n</string>
    <string name="tat10">SelfCare Reminders or Daily Affirmations:\n</string>
    <string name="tat11">Sleep Improvement Tools:\n</string>
    <string name="tat12">Coping Strategies Toolbox:\n</string>
    <string name="tat13">Mood Diary or Emotion Tracking:\n</string>
    <string name="tat14">Virtual Reality (VR) Relaxation Environments:\n</string>
    <string name="tat15">Educational Resources and Articles:\n</string>
    <string name="tat16">Gratitude Journals or Daily Reflections:\n</string>
    <string name="tat17">Progressive Stress Reduction Programs:\n</string>

    <string name="tatd1">Offer guided meditation sessions or breathing exercises within the app. These can help users relax, reduce stress, and focus on their breath to calm anxiety.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd2">Include features that guide users through mindfulness practices, such as body scans, progressive muscle relaxation, or guided imagery.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd3">Provide activities like stretching routines, gentle yoga practices, or tai chi exercises designed to alleviate stress and tension.\n</string>
    <string name="tatd4">Incorporate a feature where users can log their thoughts, feelings, or mood changes. This can help them track patterns and gain insights into their emotions.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd5">Include a library of calming sounds, nature sounds, or soothing music that users can listen to for relaxation purposes.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd6">Offer tools or techniques based on CBT principles to help users challenge negative thoughts and reframe their thinking patterns.\n</string>
    <string name="tatd7">Create a system that allows users to set achievable goals and track their progress. Celebrating small achievements can boost confidence and reduce anxiety.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd8"> Implement a feature that connects users with others experiencing similar challenges. This can provide a sense of community and support.\n</string>
    <string name="tatd9">Provide assessments to help users identify their stressors and suggest coping strategies or resources tailored to their needs.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd10">Send users regular reminders for selfcare activities or positive affirmations to boost their mood and self-esteem.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd11">Integrate tools to promote better sleep, such as sleep trackers, calming bedtime stories, or guided sleep meditations, as quality sleep can significantly impact anxiety levels.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd12">Create a repository of coping strategies and techniques for managing anxiety, such as grounding exercises, thought-stopping techniques, or self-soothing practices.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd13">Enable users to track their moods over time, allowing them to recognize patterns and better understand their emotions.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd14">For more immersive experiences, consider offering VR environments that simulate peaceful landscapes or tranquil settings to promote relaxation and mindfulness.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd15">Provide curated articles, blogs, or educational content about anxiety management, coping mechanisms, and mental health awareness.\n</string>
    <string name="tatd16">Incorporate prompts for users to reflect on things they are grateful for or encourage daily reflection on positive moments, fostering a more optimistic outlook.
\n</string>
    <string name="tatd17">Develop structured programs that gradually introduce stress-relieving activities or mindfulness exercises to help users build healthy habits and resilience over time.
\n</string>

    <string name="at_desc">Discover simple, effective strategies to ease anxiety and boost your well-being. From quick calming exercises to practical tips, we\'ve got your back on the path to a more relaxed you.</string>
    <string name="anxiety_management_tips">Anxiety Management Tips</string>

</resources>