<resources>
    <!-- main -->
    <string name="app_name">Self-MIEnd</string>
    <string name="app_icon">Self-MIEnd Icon</string>
    <string name="app_tagline">Guiding Your Path to\nMental Wellness</string>
    <string name="app_name2">Self-Mind, Self-Mend</string>
    <string name="app_startBtn">START</string>

    <!-- about fragment -->
    <string name="abt_hey">Hey There!</string>
    <string name="abt_intro">Self MIEnd is your personal companion on the journey to mental health and well-being. The application allows you to engage in a self-discovery process, providing a safe and supportive environment for self-reflection and personal growth. We provide self-assessment tests for common mental health problems for you to evaluate your mental well-being and determine whether professional help may be necessary.\n\n We also got you some activities and tips to try!</string>
    <string name="app_contBtn">Continue</string>
    <string name="app_backBtn">Back</string>

    <string name="home_title">Select Activity</string>
    <string name="home_testBtn">Tests</string>
    <string name="home_actBtn">Activities to Try</string>

    <!-- greeting and select test fragment -->
    <string name="tests_title">Select a Test</string>
    <string name="stressTest_title">Stress</string>
    <string name="internet_addictionTest_title">Internet\nAddiction</string>
    <string name="depressionTest_title">Depression</string>
    <string name="anxietyTest_title">Anxiety</string>

    <!--test fragment-->
    <string name="test_text">Test</string>
    <string name="test_question">Loading Question&#8230;</string>
    <string name="greeting_title">How\'s it going?</string>

    <!--result fragment-->
    <string name="test_result_title">Test Result</string>
    <string name="test_result_scoreText">Score:</string>
    <string name="test_result_severity_levelText">Severity Level:</string>
    <string name="temp_score">0</string>
    <string name="temp_level">Minimal</string>
    <string name="hotline_caption">Experiencing emotional hurdles?</string>
    <string name="hotline_call">Click to Find Support</string>
    <string name="backText">Back</string>
    <string name="nextText">Next</string>
    <string name="loading_questionText">Loading Question&#8230;</string>
    <string name="done_button">Done</string>

    <!--home fragment-->
    <string name="act_try">Activities\nto Try</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="exit_question">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="title_activities_tips_for_mental_well_being"><![CDATA[Tips for Mental Well-being]]></string>
    <string name="self_care_for_mental_wellness">Over-all Self-care</string>
    <string name="thankyou_message">Your wellness journey matters. Thank you!</string>
    <string name="done_question">Would you like to try the other Tests and Activities?</string>
    <string name="exitButton">Exit</string>
    <string name="several_days">Several Days</string>
    <string name="not_at_all">Not at all</string>
    <string name="more_than_half_the_days">More Than Half The Days</string>
    <string name="moderately">Moderately</string>
    <string name="a_little_bit">A Little Bit</string>
    <string name="quite_a_bit">Quite A Bit</string>
    <string name="extremely">Extremely</string>
    <string name="not_applicable">Not Applicable</string>
    <string name="rarely">Rarely</string>
    <string name="occasionally">Occasionally</string>
    <string name="often">Often</string>
    <string name="always">Always</string>
    <string name="nearly_every_day">Nearly Every Day</string>
    <string name="self_care_tips_activities"><![CDATA[Self-Care Tips & Activities]]></string>
    <string name="for_specific_areas">For specific areas:</string>
    <string name="greetings">Time for a quick mental health check! Take a moment to reflect on your well-being. If you\'ve taken any assessments, we\'re here to discuss the results and provide support and guidance.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="anxiety_test_text">Anxiety Test</string>
    <string name="depression_test_text">Depression Test</string>
    <string name="stress_test_text">Stress Test</string>
    <string name="internet_addiction_test_text">Internet Addiction Test</string>
    <string name="frequently">Frequently</string>

    <string name="display_score_label">%d</string>


    <!-- Title Strings -->
    <string name="tip_title_1">1. Practice Mindfulness Meditation:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_2">2. Establish a Routine:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_3">3. Stay Connected:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_4">4. Exercise Regularly:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_5">5. Set Realistic Goals:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_6">6. Limit Screen Time:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_7">7. Prioritize Sleep:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_8">8. Express Yourself Creatively:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_9">9. Learn to Say No:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_10">10. Practice Gratitude:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_11">11. Seek Professional Support:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_12">12. Engage in Hobbies:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_13">13. Take Breaks:\n</string>
    <string name="tip_title_14">14. Practice Self-Compassion:\n</string>

    <!-- Description Strings -->
    <string name="tip_desc_1"><![CDATA[
    • Set aside a few minutes each day to practice mindfulness meditation.\n
    • Focus on your breath and bring your attention to the present moment.\n
    • Apps like Headspace or Calm can guide you through meditation sessions.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_2"><![CDATA[
    • Create a daily schedule that includes regular sleep, meals, and breaks.\n
    • Consistent routines can provide a sense of stability and predictability.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_3"><![CDATA[
    • Maintain relationships with friends and family.\n
    • Schedule regular social activities, even if they&apos;re virtual, to stay connected.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_4"><![CDATA[
    • Engage in physical activities you enjoy, such as walking, jogging, or yoga.\n
    • Exercise releases endorphins, which can improve your mood.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_5"><![CDATA[
    • Break down large tasks into smaller, manageable goals.\n
    • Celebrate your achievements, no matter how small.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_6"><![CDATA[
    • Set boundaries for your screen time, especially on social media.\n
    • Allocate time for activities that don&apos;t involve screens, like reading or outdoor pursuits.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_7"><![CDATA[
    • Ensure you get enough restful sleep each night.\n
    • Create a calming bedtime routine to signal to your body that it&apos;s time to wind down.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_8"><![CDATA[
    • Engage in creative activities such as writing, drawing, or playing an instrument.\n
    • Expressing yourself creatively can be therapeutic.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_9"><![CDATA[
    • Set boundaries and learn to say no when you need to.\n
    • Prioritize your well-being by not overcommitting.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_10"><![CDATA[
    • Keep a gratitude journal to reflect on positive aspects of your life.\n
    • Focus on the things you&apos;re thankful for, no matter how small.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_11"><![CDATA[
    • If needed, don&apos;t hesitate to reach out to a mental health professional.\n
    • Therapy or counseling can provide valuable tools for managing stress and challenges.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_12"><![CDATA[
    • Spend time doing things you love, whether it&apos;s gardening, painting, or playing a sport.\n
    • Hobbies can bring joy and fulfillment to your life.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_13"><![CDATA[
    • Incorporate short breaks into your day to rest and recharge.\n
    • Step away from work or stressful situations to clear your mind.\n
]]></string>

    <string name="tip_desc_14"><![CDATA[
    • Be kind to yourself and recognize that everyone makes mistakes.\n
    • Treat yourself with the same kindness and understanding you would offer a friend.\n
]]></string>
    <string name="selfcare_desc">Taking care of your mental well-being is crucial for overall health and happiness. Here are some selfcare activities and tips that can contribute to your mental well-being:</string>

    <string name="disclaimer"><![CDATA[The information and tools provided by this mobile application are for informational purposes only and should not be construed as medical advice or a substitute for professional mental health care. The results of any self-assessment tools should not be used to diagnose or treat any mental health condition.\n
\n
Please note that:\n
\n
The self-assessment tools in this app are not 100% accurate and may not detect all mental health conditions.
The information provided in this app is not intended to be a complete overview of mental health and may not address all of your questions or concerns.
If you are experiencing a mental health crisis, please call a suicide hotline or go to the nearest emergency room.\n
\nWe encourage you to:
\n
Use this app as a starting point for learning more about mental health.
Talk to your doctor or a mental health professional if you have any concerns about your mental health.
Take care of yourself and seek help if you need it.
\n\n
Thank you for using our app. We hope that it helps you on your journey to better mental health.
]]></string>

    <!-- Result Scoring -->

    <!-- Anxiety -->
    <string name="anxietyR1">Minimal Anxiety</string>
    <string name="anxietyR2">Mild Anxiety</string>
    <string name="anxietyR3">Moderate Anxiety</string>
    <string name="anxietyR4">Severe Anxiety</string>

    <!-- Depression -->
    <string name="depressionR1">Minimal Depression</string>
    <string name="depressionR2">Mild Depression</string>
    <string name="depressionR3">Moderate Depression</string>
    <string name="depressionR4">Moderately Severe Depression</string>
    <string name="depressionR5">Severe Depression</string>

    <!-- Internet Addiction -->
    <string name="internetAddictionR1">Normal Level of Internet Usage</string>
    <string name="internetAddictionR2">Mild Level of Internet Usage</string>
    <string name="internetAddictionR3">Moderate Level of Internet Usage</string>
    <string name="internetAddictionR4">Severe Dependence upon the Internet</string>

    <!-- Stress -->
    <string name="stressR1">Low Stress</string>
    <string name="stressR2">Moderate Stress</string>
    <string name="stressR3">High Perceived Stress</string>

    <!-- Disclaimer -->
    <string name="disclaimerHead">Disclaimer</string>

    <!-- Anxiety Tips Strings -->
    <string name="tast1">Deep Breathing\n</string>
    <string name="tast2">Regular Exercise\n</string>
    <string name="tast3">Healthy Diet\n</string>
    <string name="tast4">Mindfulness and Meditation\n</string>
    <string name="tast5">Get Enough Sleep\n</string>
    <string name="tast6">Limit Exposure to Stress\n</string>
    <string name="tast7">Seek Support\n</string>
    <string name="tast8">Set Realistic Goals\n</string>
    <string name="tast9">Time Management\n</string>
    <string name="tast10">Limit Media Consumption\n</string>

    <string name="tasd1">Practice deep breathing exercises to calm your nervous system and reduce anxiety.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd2">Engage in regular physical activity as it helps in reducing stress and anxiety.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd3">Maintain a balanced diet and limit caffeine and sugar intake, as they can contribute to anxiety.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd4">Practice mindfulness techniques or meditation to ground yourself in the present moment and reduce anxiety.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd5">Ensure you get adequate sleep as lack of sleep can exacerbate anxiety.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd6">Ensure you get adequate sleep as lack of sleep can exacerbate anxiety.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd7">Talk to someone you trust, a friend, family member, or therapist, about your feelings and worries.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd8">Break down tasks into manageable steps to reduce overwhelming feelings.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd9">Organize your time effectively to reduce stress caused by feeling rushed or overwhelmed.\n</string>
    <string name="tasd10">Reduce exposure to distressing news or social media if it tends to increase your anxiety.\n</string>

    <!-- Internet Addiction Tips Strings -->

    <string name="tiat1">Set Boundaries\n</string>
    <string name="tiat2">Identify Triggers\n</string>
    <string name="tiat3">Limit Access\n</string>
    <string name="tiat4">Find Offline Activities\n</string>
    <string name="tiat5">Practice Mindfulness\n</string>
    <string name="tiat6">Social Interaction\n</string>
    <string name="tiat7">Create Tech-Free Zones\n</string>
    <string name="tiat8">Seek Support\n</string>
    <string name="tiat9">Digital Detox\n</string>
    <string name="tiat10">Reflect and Evaluate\n</string>

    <string name="tiad1">Establish specific times for using the internet and stick to them. Create a schedule to limit excessive usage.\n</string>
    <string name="tiad2">Recognize situations or emotions that lead to excessive internet use and find ways to address them differently.\n</string>
    <string name="tiad3">Remove or limit access to devices or apps that consume the most time and attention.\n</string>
    <string name="tiad4">Engage in hobbies, sports, or activities that dont involve screens to diversify your interests and reduce dependency on the internet..\n</string>
    <string name="tiad5">Be mindful of your online activities and take breaks to assess whether youre using the internet out of habit or necessity..\n</string>
    <string name="tiad6">Foster real-life connections by spending quality time with friends and family offline.\n</string>
    <string name="tiad7">Designate specific areas (like bedrooms or dining areas) as tech-free zones to encourage offline activities and interactions.\n</string>
    <string name="tiad8">Consider joining support groups or seeking professional help to manage and overcome internet addiction.\n</string>
    <string name="tiad9">Plan periodic breaks from the internet, whether its a day or a weekend, to reset and recalibrate your relationship with technology.\n</string>
    <string name="tiad10">Regularly assess your internet usage patterns and their impact on your life. Adjust habits accordingly to maintain a healthy balance.\n</string>

    <!-- Stress Tips Strings -->

    <string name="tst1">Deep Breathing And Relaxation:\n</string>
    <string name="tst2">Regular Exercise:\n</string>
    <string name="tst3">Healthy Eating Habits:\n</string>
    <string name="tst4">Adequete Sleep:\n</string>
    <string name="tst5">Time Management:\n</string>
    <string name="tst6">Set Boundaries:\n</string>
    <string name="tst7">Seek Support:\n</string>
    <string name="tst8">Mindfulness and Relaxation:\n</string>
    <string name="tst9">Time for Yourself:\n</string>
    <string name="tst10">Positive Outlook:\n</string>

    <string name="tsd1">Practice deep breathing, meditation, or progressive muscle relaxation to calm your mind and body.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd2">Engage in physical activities like walking, yoga, or any exercise you enjoy to reduce stress hormones and boost endorphins.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd3">Maintain a balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables, and whole grains to support your bodys stress-coping mechanisms.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd4">Ensure you get enough quality sleep as it plays a vital role in managing stress levels.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd5">Organize tasks, prioritize, and set realistic goals to reduce overwhelming feelings caused by time constraints.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd6">Learn to say no when necessary and establish boundaries to manage your commitments and avoid overload.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd7">Talk to friends, family, or a professional counselor for emotional support and guidance when dealing with stress.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd8">Practice mindfulness or engage in activities like reading, listening to music, or hobbies to relax your mind.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd9">Schedule time for activities you enjoy or for self-care to recharge and alleviate stress.\n</string>
    <string name="tsd10">Focus on the positives, cultivate gratitude, and try to adopt a more optimistic perspective on challenging situations.\n</string>


    <!-- Depression Tips Strings -->

    <string name="tdt1">Professional Help\n</string>
    <string name="tdt2">Social Support\n</string>
    <string name="tdt3">Regular Exercise\n</string>
    <string name="tdt4">Healthy Diet\n</string>
    <string name="tdt5">Sleep Hygiene\n</string>
    <string name="tdt6">Mindfulness and Meditation\n</string>
    <string name="tdt7">Avoid Isolation\n</string>
    <string name="tdt8">Set Realistic Goals\n</string>
    <string name="tdt9">Limit Stress\n</string>
    <string name="tdt10">Be Kind to Yourself\n</string>

    <string name="tdd1">Seek support from a mental health professional such as a therapist, counselor, or psychiatrist. They can provide therapy, medication, or a combination of both tailored to your needs.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd2">Connect with friends, family, or support groups. Sharing your feelings and experiences with others can alleviate feelings of isolation and offer emotional support.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd3">Engage in regular physical activity as it helps in releasing endorphins, improving mood, and reducing symptoms of depression.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd4">Eat a well-balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables, whole grains, and lean proteins. Certain nutrients can positively impact mood and energy levels.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd5">Maintain a regular sleep schedule and create a relaxing bedtime routine. Quality sleep is crucial for mental health.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd6">Practice mindfulness, meditation, or deep breathing exercises to reduce stress and promote relaxation.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd7">Make efforts to stay connected with others, even when you might feel like withdrawing. Social interaction is important for mental well-being.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd8">Break tasks into manageable steps and set achievable goals to avoid feeling overwhelmed by large tasks.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd9">Identify and minimize stress triggers. Use stress reduction techniques like yoga, journaling, or hobbies to cope with stress.\n</string>
    <string name="tdd10">Practice self-compassion and avoid self-criticism. Treat yourself with kindness and understanding, acknowledging that recovery from depression takes time.\n</string>

    <!-- others -->

    <string name="at_desc">Discover simple, effective strategies to ease anxiety and boost your well-being. From quick calming exercises to practical tips, we\'ve got your back on the path to a more relaxed you.</string>
    <string name="anxiety_management_tips">Anxiety Management Tips</string>
    <string name="dt">Discover practical strategies and uplifting activities to support your well-being, guiding you toward a brighter path.</string>
    <string name="depression_management_tips">Depression Management Tips</string>
    <string name="internet_addiction_management_tips">Internet Addiction Management Tips</string>
    <string name="ia_desc">Balance your digital life with our Internet Addiction Tips app. Quick strategies to manage screen time and promote a healthier online-offline balance.</string>
    <string name="st_desc">Explore quick and effective strategies to ease tension, enhance well-being, and bring more balance to your daily life. From mindful moments to practical stress-busting tips, find your path to a calmer, more resilient you.</string>
    <string name="how_are_you_nlet_s_talk">How are you? Let\'s talk!</string>
    <string name="land_line">1553</string>
    <string name="landline_text">Luzon Wide landline toll-fee</string>
    <string name="globe_tm_subscribers">GLOBE/TM Subscribers</string>
    <string name="globe_hotlines">09663514518\n09178998727\n0917899USAP</string>
    <string name="smart_hotline">09086392672</string>
    <string name="done_btn">Done</string>
    <string name="subscribers_sim">SMART/SUN/TNT Subscribers</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="sample_result_advice">Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod</string>
    <string name="stress_management_tips">Stress Management Tips</string>

</resources>